♪The neon lights before the French windows shining at 3 AM♪
♪ أضواء النيون أمام النوافذ الفرنسية تلمع الساعة 3 فجرا ♪
♪The pile of old photos is getting dusty♪
كومة الصور القديمة تتغبر
♪It's the season of reunion♪
♪ إنه موسم لم الشمل ♪
♪The gentle breeze is brushing my cheek♪
النسيم اللطيف يفرش خدي
♪You failed to see me in the crowd♪
♪ لقد فشلت في رؤيتي وسط الحشد ♪
♪The neon lights are bright, but I can't find you in the crowd♪
♪ أضواء النيون ساطعة لكن لا أجدك وسط الزحام
♪I can sense that you're avoiding me♪
♪ أستطيع أن أشعر أنك تتجنبني
♪On the empty street♪
في الشارع الخالي ♪
♪Where the neon lights are shining alone♪
حيث تسطع أضواء النيون وحدها
♪Just like our reunion♪
♪ تمامًا مثل لم شملنا ♪
♪The neon lights are blinking, and I failed to get closer to you♪
♪ أضواء النيون تومض ، وفشلت في الاقتراب منك
♪Some have already forgotten♪
♪ لقد نسي البعض بالفعل
♪The fragments of memories♪
شظايا الذكريات ♪
♪Will fade one day like neon lights♪
♪ سوف تتلاشى يومًا ما مثل أضواء النيون
♪By then, can we get the spark back?♪
♪ بحلول ذلك الوقت ، هل يمكننا استعادة الشرارة؟
[To Be A Brave One]
[أن تكون شجاعًا]
[Episode 33]
[الحلقة 33]
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for staying in the company.
للبقاء في الشركة.
Some time ago,
قبل حين،
a lot
كثيراً
happened
حدث
to Yimi Capital and me.
إلى Yimi Capital ولي.
I...
أنا...
wish to apologize to you
أتمنى أن أعتذر لك
for letting you down.
لإحباطك.
I wanted to bring good news to the company,
أردت أن أحمل أخبارًا جيدة للشركة ،
but...
لكن...
Sorry.
آسف.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for your contributions to the company.
لمساهماتك في الشركة.
I hope you are proud of yourself.
أتمنى أن تكون فخوراً بنفسك.
At the same time,
في نفس الوقت،
I'm also
انا ايضا
proud about my decision.
فخور بقراري.
Running a company
إدارة شركة
is one of the missions I have in my life,
هي إحدى المهام التي أمتلكها في حياتي ،
but
لكن
I made mistakes.
أنا ارتكبت أخطاء.
I am responsible.
أنا مسؤول.
So, in the remaining days,
لذلك ، في الأيام المتبقية ،
I can't be with you.
لا استطيع ان اكون معك.
I must stop
يجب أن أتوقف
and ponder over some issues.
وتفكر مليا في بعض القضايا.
If, according to the company's accounting group,
إذا ، وفقًا لمجموعة محاسبة الشركة ،
there is remaining money in our account,
هناك أموال متبقية في حسابنا ،
I'll pay everyone the severance pay.
سأدفع لكل شخص مكافأة نهاية الخدمة.
Over here,
هنا،
I sincerely wish
أتمنى بصدق
that you face yourself and your life
أن تواجه نفسك وحياتك
bravely.
بشجاعة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Beginning tomorrow,
ابتداء من غد
this will belong to someone else.
هذا سوف ينتمي إلى شخص آخر.
You lost this home because of me.
لقد فقدت هذا المنزل بسببي.
Sorry.
آسف.
Don't say sorry.
لا تقل آسف.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
We only lost
لقد خسرنا فقط
this house
هذا البيت
and this courtyard.
وهذا الفناء.
To begin with,
لنبدء ب،
we don't belong here.
نحن لا ننتمي إلى هنا.
Home is where the family is,
المنزل هو مكان الأسرة ،
with the three of us.
مع ثلاثتنا.
I have signed.
لقد وقعت.
You can sign it.
يمكنك التوقيع عليه.
I won't.
أنا لن.
I won't leave you now.
لن أتركك الآن.
You should find someone better.
يجب أن تجد شخصًا أفضل.
I don't deserve you.
أنا لا أستحقك.
There is no one better.
لا يوجد احد افضل.
After going through so many things all our life,
بعد أن مررنا بالعديد من الأشياء طوال حياتنا ،
why are you talking about deserving or not,
لماذا تتحدث عن الاستحقاق أم لا ،
Zhou Yuan?
تشو يوان؟
I don't care what you say,
لا يهمني ما تقول
or what you want to do today,
أو ماذا تريد أن تفعل اليوم ،
I won't let go.
لن اتركها.
I won't leave you at this juncture.
لن أتركك في هذا المنعطف.
We cannot start over as we wish.
لا يمكننا أن نبدأ من جديد كما نتمنى.
I made a mistake.
لقد ارتكبت خطأ.
I have to face the consequences, understand?
لا بد لي من مواجهة العواقب ، فهم؟
You can do that
تستطيع فعل ذلك
with me by your side.
معي بجانبك.
From childhood to adulthood,
من الطفولة إلى البلوغ ،
we had undertaken so many things together.
لقد قمنا بالعديد من الأشياء معًا.
Don't keep thinking you made a mistake
لا تستمر في التفكير في أنك ارتكبت خطأ
and push me aside.
ودفعني جانبا.
I can face it with you.
أستطيع أن أواجهها معك.
As long as we stay together,
طالما بقينا معًا ،
we can start over
يمكننا البدء من جديد
and get through it. Okay?
وتجاوزها.  تمام؟
Mi Lu,
مي لو ،
don't you understand?
الا تفهم
The person I loved for so many years wasn't you.
الشخص الذي أحببته لسنوات عديدة لم يكن أنت.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
You are just a substitute!
أنت مجرد بديل!
Don't regard yourself as Yiyi's biological mother.
لا تعتبر نفسك والدة ييي البيولوجية.
I had no one to take care of Yiyi
لم يكن لدي من يعتني بـ Yiyi
and got you to stay with him.
وجعلك تبقى معه.
Don't describe our past so beautifully,
لا تصف ماضينا بشكل جميل جدا ،
okay?
حسنا؟
Do you think I needed you all along?
هل تعتقد أنني كنت بحاجة لك طوال الوقت؟
I just needed a partner by my side.
أنا فقط بحاجة إلى شريك بجانبي.
The moment I met An Yu,
في اللحظة التي قابلت فيها آن يو ،
I didn't need you anymore!
لم أعد بحاجة إليك!
Okay. Okay.
تمام.  تمام.
Sign it now.
وقع عليه الآن.
I have signed.
لقد وقعت.
By the way,
على فكرة،
is this card under your name?
هل هذه البطاقة باسمك
Take it.
خذها.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I don't want to have anything to do with you.
لا أريد أن أفعل أي شيء معك.
This is
هذا هو
as far as we go!
بقدر ما نذهب!
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
I bought the last bowl of shrimp wonton.
لقد اشتريت آخر صحن من فطيرة باللحم الروبيان.
Am I awesome?
هل انا رائع؟
Only one?
واحد فقط؟
I also bought the fresh meat flavor.
كما أنني اشتريت نكهة اللحم الطازج.
We'll share.
سوف نشارك.
Is this shrimp?
هل هذا جمبري؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's fresh shrimp.
إنه جمبري طازج.
I'll just eat the meat flavor.
سآكل فقط نكهة اللحم.
You take the shrimp flavor.
تأخذ نكهة الجمبري.
We'll share.
سوف نشارك.
Okay.
تمام.
It's hot.
إنه حار.
A bit hot.
حار قليلا.
Careful.
حذر.
Here.
هنا.
You first.
أنت أولاً.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
The shrimp flavor is the best.
نكهة الجمبري هي الأفضل.
You look silly.
تبدو سخيفا.
You call me silly?
أنت تدعوني سخيفة؟
If I'm silly,
إذا كنت سخيفة ،
you are sillier.
انت اكثر ذكاء.
I'm not silly.
أنا لست سخيفا.
Aren't you silly?
ألست سخيفة؟
You're silly enough to like me.
أنت سخيف بما يكفي لمحبتي.
Ha,
ها
you wish!
انت تتمنى!
Okay.
تمام.
I wish!
أتمنى!
Here, have some soup.
هنا ، تناول بعض الحساء.
My biggest wish
أمنيتي الكبرى
is for us to be together.
هو أن نكون معًا.
As for Fangfang,
أما بالنسبة لـ Fangfang ،
I wish he will be safe.
أتمنى أن يكون بأمان.
Other things don't matter.
أشياء أخرى لا تهم.
That day, on the way to Nankou Village,
في ذلك اليوم ، في الطريق إلى قرية نانكو ،
you said something in the car.
قلت شيئا في السيارة.
You said
أنت قلت
that every parent has moments of despair.
أن كل والد لديه لحظات من اليأس.
Sometimes,
بعض الأحيان،
a parent would think of dying with their child.
قد يفكر أحد الوالدين في الموت مع طفله.
Was that about you?
هل كان هذا عنك
Forget that.
انس هذا.
Did you...
هل فعلت...
♪The same color♪
نفس اللون ♪
really want to do that?
حقا تريد أن تفعل ذلك؟
♪In the same corner♪
في نفس الزاوية ♪
At that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
Fangfang just got into an accident.
وقع Fangfang للتو في حادث.
It was the greatest blow for me.
كانت أكبر ضربة بالنسبة لي.
I collapsed.
انهارت.
♪The same extremes♪
♪ نفس النهايات ♪
♪Who said two like poles would repel?♪
♪ من قال أن قطبين متشابهين سيتنافران؟
So,
لذا،
every day...
كل يوم...
♪You just don't know how to embrace♪
♪ أنت فقط لا تعرف كيف تحتضن ♪
I stayed at his bedside.
مكثت بجانب سريره.
I was sleepless night after night.
كنت بلا نوم ليلة بعد ليلة.
Every day, I thought about
كنت أفكر في كل يوم
what I should do next.
ماذا علي أن أفعل بعد ذلك.
Maybe I should die with Fangfang.
ربما يجب أن أموت مع Fangfang.
♪How stubborn can we be♪
♪ كيف يمكن أن نكون عنيدين ♪
I thought about everything.
فكرت في كل شيء.
♪We're all the same♪
♪ نحن جميعًا متشابهون
Sometimes, when I thought about
في بعض الأحيان ، عندما كنت أفكر
♪What rules are there♪
ما هي القواعد الموجودة ♪
how you and Fangfang
كيف أنت و Fangfang
♪To stop souls from merging together♪
لمنع النفوس من الاندماج ♪
going through this,
يمر بهذا ،
I felt bad.
شعرت بالسوء.
It hurts like a dagger stabbing in my heart.
يؤلمني مثل طعن خنجر في قلبي.
I hate myself
أنا أكره نفسي
for not meeting you sooner
لعدم مقابلتك عاجلا
♪The same ups and downs♪
♪ نفس الصعود والهبوط ♪
and stay by your side earlier,
والبقاء بجانبك في وقت سابق ،
♪No more strength to pretend♪
♪ لا مزيد من القوة للتظاهر
to be with you and Fangfang.
أن أكون معك و Fangfang.
♪Unafraid of enjoying the hardships♪
لا تخشى الاستمتاع بالمصاعب
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
♪For you are with me♪
لأنك معي
I bore the ordeal
لقد تحملت المحنة
and made it through.
وتمكنت من ذلك.
♪The same sadness♪
نفس الحزن ♪
♪Singing the same song♪
غناء نفس الأغنية ♪
You don't have to suffer anymore.
ليس عليك أن تعاني بعد الآن.
♪We're not afraid of setbacks♪
♪ لسنا خائفين من الانتكاسات ♪
I'll be there for you.
ستجدني حين تحتاجني.
You don't have to act tough anymore.
ليس عليك التصرف بحزم بعد الآن.
♪All we want is an outcome♪
كل ما نريده هو نتيجة ♪
I will always stay with you.
سأبقى دائما معك.
♪We're all the same♪
♪ نحن جميعًا متشابهون
I'll be with you and Fangfang.
سأكون معك ومع Fangfang.
♪But we're painted differently♪
♪ لكننا رسمنا بشكل مختلف ♪
♪We stay stoic even when we cry or smile♪
♪ نبقى رزينين حتى عندما نبكي أو نبتسم
You look silly.
تبدو سخيفا.
♪The flower that blooms secretly at night♪
الزهرة التي تتفتح سرا في الليل ♪
I'll stay with you and look silly forever.
سأبقى معك وأبدو سخيفة إلى الأبد.
♪We're all the same♪
♪ نحن جميعًا متشابهون
Even if you shoo me away, I won't leave.
حتى لو طردتني بعيدًا ، فلن أغادر.
♪We seek approvals♪
♪ نسعى للحصول على الموافقات ♪
I won't drive you away.
لن أقوم بإبعادك.
♪What rules are there♪
ما هي القواعد الموجودة ♪
♪To stop souls from merging together?♪
♪ لمنع النفوس من الاندماج معًا؟ ♪
Did his hand move?
هل تحركت يده؟
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
It moved again.
تحركت مرة أخرى.
Fangfang!
فانغفانغ!
Fangfang, can you hear me?
Fangfang ، هل تسمعني؟
Fangfang,
فانغفانغ ،
can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
Fangfang.
فانغفانغ.
Quick.
سريع.
Get the doctor.
احصل على الطبيب.
Okay.
تمام.
Fangfang.
فانغفانغ.
Doctor.
طبيب.
Fangfang!
فانغفانغ!
Can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
Mom is here.
أمي هنا.
It's Mom, Fangfang.
إنها أمي ، Fangfang.
Fangfang.
فانغفانغ.
Fangfang!
فانغفانغ!
Taking care of a child can be exhausting.
قد تكون رعاية الطفل مرهقة.
I had a hard time getting him to sleep.
لقد واجهت صعوبة في جعله ينام.
How about we take him out to play
ماذا لو أخرجناه للعب
after he wakes up?
بعد أن يستيقظ؟
His mood...
مزاجه ...
I'll go.
سأذهب.
I'm closer.
أنا أقرب.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Are you Ms. An Yu?
هل أنت السيدة آن يو؟
Your express mail.
بريدك السريع.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[Agreement on Child Custody Modification]
[اتفاقية تعديل حضانة الأطفال]
[Share Proxy Agreement]
[مشاركة اتفاقية الوكيل]
They're from Zhou Yuan.
إنهم من Zhou Yuan.
[Police]
[شرطة]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello,
مرحبًا،
An Yu.
آن يو.
Did you receive the documents?
هل استلمت الوثائق؟
I just did.
فعلتها للتو.
Good.
جيد.
With you taking care of Yiyi,
مع رعاية Yiyi ،
I don't have to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
Although he won't call you Mommy just yet,
على الرغم من أنه لن يتصل بك يا أمي بعد ،
don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You and he share a bond.
أنت وهو يتقاسمان السند.
Before long,
من قبل فترة طويلة،
he'll accept you as his mother.
سيقبلك بصفتك والدته.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
[Zhou Yuan]
[تشو يوان]
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't do anything stupid anymore.
لن أفعل أي شيء غبي بعد الآن.
Zhuoyue's shares
أسهم Zhuoyue ل
are meaningless to me already.
لا معنى لها بالنسبة لي بالفعل.
Your dad helped mine.
والدك ساعدني.
By right,
بالحق ،
these shares should be yours.
يجب أن تكون هذه الأسهم لك.
Moreover, in your hands,
علاوة على ذلك ، بين يديك ،
I believe
أعتقد
they'll become more valuable
سيصبحون أكثر قيمة
and meaningful.
وذات مغزى.
Why did you suddenly do this?
لماذا فعلت هذا فجأة؟
Are you sure you're okay?
هل أنت متأكد أنك بخير؟
An Yu,
آن يو ،
to you
لك
and your dad,
ووالدك
I should say sorry.
يجب أن أقول آسف.
I know
أنا أعرف
that an apology is far from being enough.
أن الاعتذار بعيد عن أن يكون كافياً.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will tell the police everything
سأخبر الشرطة بكل شيء
and accept the due punishment.
وقبول العقوبة الواجبة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Can I help you?
أيمكنني مساعدتك؟
My name is Zhou Yuan.
اسمي تشو يوان.
My true name is Xiao Yong.
اسمي الحقيقي شياو يونغ.
I came to turn myself in.
جئت لتسليم نفسي.
Dad.
أب.
You can smoke a cigarette today.
يمكنك تدخين سيجارة اليوم.
It was not allowed before,
لم يكن مسموحا به من قبل ،
[Devoted Father, An Wenbin] but today,
[الأب المخلص ، وينبين] ولكن اليوم ،
I made an exception.
لقد قمت باستثناء.
Mr. An,
السيد آن ،
I brought you some wine.
أحضرت لك بعض النبيذ.
Drink as much as you like
اشرب بقدر ما تريد
because we have good news for you.
لأن لدينا أخبار جيدة لك.
An Yu will tell you personally.
سيخبرك يو بشكل شخصي.
Over the last few months,
خلال الأشهر القليلة الماضية ،
a lot has happened.
حدث الكثير.
Maybe you have seen them from heaven.
ربما رأيتهم من السماء.
Thanks to Mr. Xiao's letter,
بفضل رسالة السيد زياو ،
we found out the truth.
اكتشفنا الحقيقة.
Thanks to that letter,
بفضل تلك الرسالة ،
Zhou Yuan stopped before it was too late.
توقف Zhou Yuan قبل فوات الأوان.
He didn't repeat his mistakes.
لم يكرر أخطائه.
He has turned himself in.
لقد سلم نفسه.
I believe he'll turn over a new leaf.
أعتقد أنه سوف يفتح صفحة جديدة.
Yiyi
ييي
has returned to my side,
عاد إلى جانبي ،
but he needs more time
لكنه يحتاج إلى مزيد من الوقت
to adapt.
تكيف.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Dad, believe me.
يا أبي ، صدقني.
I can be a good mother.
يمكنني أن أكون أم جيدة.
When Yiyi is older
عندما يكبر Yiyi
and more sensible,
وأكثر منطقية ،
I will bring him here
سوف أحضره هنا
and let him call you Grandpa.
ودعه يناديك يا جدي.
Dad,
أب،
it is over.
انتهى.
This is how things stand.
هكذا تسير الأمور.
Starting from today,
بدءا من اليوم،
An Yu is the legal guardian of Yiyi.
An Yu هو الوصي القانوني على Yiyi.
She has full custody of him.
لديها وصاية كاملة عليه.
Let's cooperate with her.
دعونا نتعاون معها.
This includes the community
وهذا يشمل المجتمع
and school.
والمدرسة.
Okay.
تمام.
Thank you for your trust in me.
شكرا لك على ثقتك بي.
I'll do my best to take care of Yiyi.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي لرعاية Yiyi.
I won't let him suffer any grievances.
لن أتركه يعاني من أي شكاوى.
A child may not be able to accept this right away.
قد لا يتمكن الطفل من قبول هذا على الفور.
Take it slow.
على مهلك.
If necessary,
اذا كان ضروري،
you can come to me.
يمكنك المجيء الي.
We'll try to cooperate with you
سنحاول التعاون معك
and see how to make him
ونرى كيف تصنعه
accept his new environment.
تقبل بيئته الجديدة.
Okay.
تمام.
That's all.
هذا كل شئ.
I have to leave.
يجب علي أن أغادر.
Thank you all.
شكرا لكم جميعا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
School is over.
المدرسة انتهت.
The kids will be out soon.
سيخرج الأطفال قريباً.
I'll go in and check on them.
سأدخل وأتفقدهم.
Okay, thank you.
حسنا شكرا لك.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Miss An.
ملكة جمال آن.
I will take you home today, okay?
سوف آخذك للمنزل اليوم ، حسنا؟
Where are my daddy and mommy?
أين أبي وأمي؟
Well,
نحن سوف،
they are a bit busy.
هم مشغولون قليلا.
You'll go to my place
ستذهب إلى مكاني
and stay for a few days.
والبقاء لبضعة أيام.
No way.
مستحيل.
I will wait for
سأنتظر ل
Mommy and Daddy.
امي وابي.
However, your mommy and daddy
ومع ذلك ، والدتك وأمك
have important matters to attend to.
لديك أمور مهمة للحضور إليها.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I want Mommy and Daddy.
أريد أمي وأبي.
Be a good boy, Yiyi.
كن ولدا طيبا ، يييي.
Can you go with me?
اتستطيع ان تذهب معى؟
Come out first.
اخرج أولا.
I'll wait for Mommy and Daddy.
سأنتظر أمي وأبي.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Dark Knight!
فارس الظلام!
Are you the Dark Knight?
هل أنت فارس الظلام؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I am Moon,
انا القمر
the Dark Knight.
فارس الظلام.
The Dark Knight is here to pick Yiyi up.
فارس الظلام هنا لاختيار Yiyi.
Is it true, Dark Knight?
هل هذا صحيح يا دارك نايت؟
Yes.
نعم.
Dark Knight, let's go eat fries!
فارس الظلام ، دعنا نأكل البطاطا المقلية!
McDonald's!
ماكدونالدز!
You want French fries?
تريد بطاطس مقلية؟
Of course, that's fine.
بالطبع ، هذا جيد.
Let's go together.
لنذهب معا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Dark Knight,
فارس الظلام
when we're out there,
عندما نكون هناك
I want to play with you.
اريدان العب معك.
(When I got him to bed,)
(عندما جعلته ينام)
(I told him a story.)
(أخبرته قصة).
(It was the only fairy tale I knew.)
(كانت الحكاية الخيالية الوحيدة التي عرفتها).
I told him
اخبرته
that he doesn't need to worry.
أنه لا داعي للقلق.
No matter what difficulties he encounters,
مهما كانت الصعوبات التي يواجهها ،
the Dark Knight will come to his rescue.
سوف يأتي فارس الظلام لإنقاذه.
Correct?
صحيح؟
Of course,
بالطبع،
the Dark Knight will protect you both.
سوف يحميك فارس الظلام كلاكما.
Your meal is here.
وجبتك هنا.
Mommy.
أمي.
Look! What is that?
نظرة!  ما هذا؟
Does it smell good?
أنها لا رائحة طيبة؟
Yes.
نعم.
It smells so good.
رائحتها جيدة جدا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Can I take a photo with you?
هل يمكنني ان اتصور معك؟
He is the Dark Knight.
إنه فارس الظلام.
His name is Moon.
اسمه مون.
He is my good friend.
هو صديقي العزيز.
You're lying.
انت تكذب.
The Dark Knight does not exist in this world.
فارس الظلام غير موجود في هذا العالم.
Dark Knight, tell them
أخبرهم فارس الظلام
that you are the Dark Knight.
أنك فارس الظلام.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
I am the Dark Knight.
أنا فارس الظلام.
My name is Moon.
اسمي مون.
He lied.
هو كذب.
He is not the Dark Knight.
إنه ليس فارس الظلام.
Look.
نظرة.
He is a human.
إنه إنسان.
Liar. Let's go!
كذاب.  لنذهب!
It's you.
انه انت.
You are a bad guy.
انت رجل سيء
I don't want you!
لا اريدك!
Yiyi.
ييي.
Don't run around.
لا تركض.
Ms. Mi,
السيدة مي ،
you've dealt with so many divorce cases in court.
لقد تعاملت مع العديد من قضايا الطلاق في المحكمة.
In this field,
في هذا الحقل،
you're more professional than me.
أنت أكثر احترافًا مني.
I want to hear your opinion.
أريد أن أسمع رأيك.
Do I have a chance
هل لدي فرصة
to get back the custody?
لاستعادة الحضانة؟
It's not totally impossible,
إنه ليس مستحيلًا تمامًا ،
but the child's current custody
لكن حضانة الطفل الحالية
has been modified.
تم التعديل.
And this kind of thing happened to the child's father.
وحدث هذا النوع من الأشياء لوالد الطفل.
The other party is the child's biological mother.
الطرف الآخر هو والدة الطفل البيولوجية.
I could only say
أستطيع أن أقول فقط
that it's very unlikely.
أنه من غير المحتمل جدًا.
Even if I only have
حتى لو كان لدي فقط
a 0.01-percent hope,
أمل 0.01 في المئة ،
I want to fight for it.
اريد ان اقاتل من اجل ذلك
Ms. Mi,
السيدة مي ،
you know
أنت تعرف
that this process
أن هذه العملية
is very long and painful.
طويلة جدا ومؤلمة.
I will get his custody back
سأستعيد حضانته
at all costs.
باي ثمن.
Help me, please.
ساعدني من فضلك.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll try my best.
سأبذل جهدي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Yiyi finally fell asleep.
يييي أخيرًا نام.
We rarely have time to rest.
نادرا ما يكون لدينا وقت للراحة.
Where are they?
أين هم؟
In the room.
في الغرفة.
I'll lower my voice.
سوف أخفض صوتي.
Don't take it to heart.
لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
Is it very difficult
انه من الصعب جدا
to care for a child?
لرعاية طفل؟
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
We are first-time parents.
نحن آباء لأول مرة.
Sometimes, we can't handle him.
في بعض الأحيان ، لا يمكننا التعامل معه.
What if
ماذا إذا
he is very stubborn?
هو عنيد جدا؟
Aren't we stubborn too?
ألسنا عنيدين أيضًا؟
What should we do
ماذا علينا ان نفعل
to change his mind?
لتغيير رأيه؟
Time will.
الوقت سيفعل.
If we can't change him,
إذا لم نتمكن من تغييره ،
we don't have to.
لسنا مضطرين لذلك.
We can just compromise
يمكننا فقط تقديم تنازلات
and find
ويجد
a way
بعيد
to coexist.
للتعايش.
Mutual tolerance.
التسامح المتبادل.
Shao Moli,
شاو مولي
how long have we not gone on a date?
منذ متى لم نذهب في موعد؟
Right.
الصحيح.
How can I work and forget life?
كيف أعمل وأنسى الحياة؟
How can you forget your motto?
كيف تنسى شعارك؟
Tomorrow, I will make arrangements immediately.
غدا ، سأقوم بالترتيبات على الفور.
Okay?
تمام؟
Deal.
صفقة.
I have an idea.
لدي فكرة.
I want to sell some of Zhuoyue's shares
أريد بيع بعض أسهم Zhuoyue
and buy the old house.
وشراء البيت القديم.
Yiyi grew up there.
نشأ Yiyi هناك.
He'll feel safe living there.
سيشعر بالأمان عند العيش هناك.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Let's plan that, then.
دعنا نخطط لذلك ، إذن.
I feel tired after drinking wine.
أشعر بالتعب بعد شرب الخمر.
You've worked hard.
لقد عملت بجد.
Fortunately, I have a Husky.
لحسن الحظ ، لدي هاسكي.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
You scared me.
لقد أخفتني.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
To visit you.
لأزورك.
Okay.
تمام.
Come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Why are you staying here?
لماذا تقيم هنا؟
Can you get used to it?
هل يمكنك التعود على ذلك؟
If not,
ان لم،
I'll find you another place tomorrow.
سأجد لك مكانًا آخر غدًا.
No need.
لا حاجة.
This place is not bad.
هذا المكان ليس سيئا.
How do you have your meals here?
كيف تتناول وجباتك هنا؟
Call me anytime if you want to eat anything.
اتصل بي في أي وقت إذا كنت تريد أن تأكل أي شيء.
I'll send it to you.
سأرسله لك.
Ding, I remember you told me before
دينغ ، أتذكر أنك أخبرتني من قبل
that your father died young.
أن والدك مات صغيرًا.
You have a sister
لديك أخت
and mother, right?
ووالدتي ، أليس كذلك؟
I'll give you an additional six months' salary.
سأعطيك راتب ستة أشهر إضافية.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I...
أنا...
You have worked hard all these years.
لقد عملت بجد كل هذه السنوات.
You have done a lot for my family.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجل عائلتي.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
أشكرك من أعماق قلبي.
Take the money and find a new job.
خذ المال وابحث عن وظيفة جديدة.
Later, get a girlfriend,
لاحقًا ، احصل على صديقة ،
get married, and start your family.
تزوج وابدأ أسرتك.
Start a new life.
إبدأ حياة جديدة.
I still have some work to do.
لا يزال لدي بعض العمل لأقوم به.
If there is nothing else, head back first.
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر ، عد أولاً.
I'm doing well.
أنا على ما يرام.
I'll leave, then.
سأرحل ، إذن.
(Thank you, Kai.)
(شكرا لك كاي.)
It's nothing.
إنه لاشيء.
Take a break.
خذ استراحة.
Go ahead and chat.
انطلق ودردش.
What's the matter with you?
ما خطبك؟
You're moving out.
أنت تخرج.
I'll miss you.
سأشتاق إلك.
Why are you suddenly so sad?
لماذا أنت حزين جدا فجأة؟
Sad?
حزين؟
I don't want you to leave me.
لا أريدك أن تتركني.
I'm leaving you.
انا سأتركك.
I live close by.
أنا أعيش في الجوار.
By taxi, you pay the basic charge.
بواسطة سيارة أجرة ، تدفع الرسوم الأساسية.
Right?
حق؟
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
we will meet every day at the company.
سنلتقي كل يوم في الشركة.
I can't bother you at any time.
لا أستطيع أن أزعجك في أي وقت.
You wish!
انت تتمنى!
I'll bother you every day and at any time.
سوف أزعجك كل يوم وفي أي وقت.
In the future, Kai and Lailai will babysit for me.
في المستقبل ، سوف يرعاني كاي وليلي.
Right?
حق؟
Absolutely.
قطعاً.
I want to test Kai's ability to take care of a child.
أريد اختبار قدرة كاي على رعاية طفل.
Are you planning?
هل تخطط؟
No.
رقم.
Hello, Shao Moli.
مرحبا شاو مولي.
How is the packing over there?
كيف هي التعبئة هناك؟
Kai and Lailai are helping me.
يساعدني كاي وليلي.
We're almost done.
نحن على وشك الانتهاء.
I'm almost done over here too.
أنا على وشك الانتهاء من هنا أيضًا.
You can directly take Yiyi here later.
يمكنك أن تأخذ Yiyi مباشرة هنا لاحقًا.
I'll leave right away when I'm done.
سأغادر على الفور عندما أنتهي.
I won't let him see me.
لن أتركه يراني.
You're so nice.
أنت لطيف جدا.
Love you.
أحبك.
What?
ماذا؟
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Stay put.
ابق على وضعك.
I'll take a photo for you.
سآخذ صورة لك.
That's it.
هذا هو.
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
I caught you.
مسكتك.
You lost weight.
لقد فقدت وزنا.
He stole a kiss.
سرق قبلة.
Is this a stolen kiss?
هل هذه قبلة مسروقة؟
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Yiyi,
يييي ،
what happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Why are you looking so down?
لماذا تنظر إلى هذا الأسفل؟
Miss An,
آنسة آن ،
why aren't my daddy and mommy
لماذا لا أبي وأمي
back yet?
العودة بعد؟
I miss them.
أفتقدهم.
I miss Bumblebee, too.
أنا أيضا أفتقد Bumblebee.
Well, Yiyi,
حسنًا ، Yiyi ،
I'll take you somewhere.
سآخذك إلى مكان ما.
Where?
أين؟
We'll visit Bumblebee.
سنقوم بزيارة بامبلبي.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Look. Where are we?
نظرة.  اين نحن؟
We're home.
نحن في المنزل.
Yiyi,
يييي ،
what's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
We're home.
نحن في المنزل.
Why do you still look so down?
لماذا ما زلت تنظر إلى هذا الحد؟
I thought
اعتقدت
you were taking me to see Mommy.
كنت تأخذني لرؤية أمي.
I heard that the villa was auctioned off.
سمعت أن الفيلا تم بيعها بالمزاد العلني.
I immediately knew it must be you.
عرفت على الفور أنه يجب أن يكون أنت.
This is good.
هذا جيد.
Yiyi doesn't have to leave his home.
لا يتعين على Yiyi مغادرة منزله.
Can I visit every week?
هل يمكنني الزيارة كل أسبوع؟
Every Saturday.
كل سبت.
You can come and see him.
يمكنك المجيء لرؤيته.
What about the weekdays, then?
ماذا عن أيام الأسبوع إذن؟
When I miss him,
عندما افتقده
can I see him?
هل يمكنني رؤيته؟
I raised him up from small.
لقد رفعته من الصغير.
I'm afraid when he doesn't see me,
أخشى عندما لا يراني ،
he will cry.
سيبكي.
He will look for me.
سوف يبحث عني.
He might not be able to sleep.
قد لا يكون قادرًا على النوم.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll visit him every Saturday.
سوف أزوره كل يوم سبت.
Even for one moment.
حتى للحظة واحدة.
Mommy.
أمي.
Yiyi.
ييي.
I've missed you so much.
لقد افتقدتك كثيرا.
Mommy.
أمي.
I've missed you too.
افتقدتك ايضا.
I've missed you so much.
لقد افتقدتك كثيرا.
Mommy.
أمي.
Why hasn't Daddy come back?
لماذا لم يعد أبي؟
Daddy?
بابي؟
He has important work to do.
لديه عمل مهم للقيام به.
I want to be with Daddy.
أريد أن أكون مع أبي.
You miss your daddy, don't you?
أنت تفتقد والدك ، أليس كذلك؟
He has to work hard.
عليه أن يعمل بجد.
If he works hard,
إذا كان يعمل بجد ،
he will make money to buy toys for you.
سيكسب المال لشراء ألعاب لك.
Right?
حق؟
I don't want toys.
لا اريد اللعب.
I don't want to make Daddy work so hard.
لا أريد أن أجعل أبي يعمل بجد.
You don't want to make Daddy work so hard?
ألا تريد أن تجعل أبي يعمل بجد؟
I know you are the most sensible kid.
أعلم أنك أكثر طفل عقلاني.
You're a good boy.
أنت فتى جيد.
Listen to Mommy.
استمع إلى ماما.
Eat well,
كل جيدا،
sleep tight,
نوما عميقا،
and work hard to grow taller.
والعمل الجاد لزيادة الطول.
When you are tall,
عندما تكون طويل القامة
Daddy will come back. Okay?
سيعود أبي.  تمام؟
I'll eat well, drink milk,
سوف آكل جيدا ، أشرب الحليب ،
and grow tall.
وتنمو طويلا.
You're awesome.
انت رائع.
Look at how cold your little hands are.
انظر إلى مدى برودة يديك الصغيرتين.
Let me make them warm.
اسمحوا لي أن أجعلها دافئة.
I'm going off today.
انا ذاهب اليوم.
I have something to do. Okay?
لدي شي لأقوم به.  تمام؟
Listen to Miss An.
استمع إلى Miss An.
Mommy, where are you going?
أمي ، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Won't you accompany me to play the piano?
ألن ترافقني لأعزف على البيانو؟
Of course, I want to do that,
بالطبع ، أريد أن أفعل ذلك ،
but...
لكن...
but Mommy has other things to do.
لكن الأم لديها أشياء أخرى لتفعلها.
Be a good boy.
كن ولدا جيدا.
I'll come back to see you in a while.
سأعود لرؤيتك بعد قليل.
Okay?
تمام؟
Be a good boy.
كن ولدا جيدا.
I have to leave now.
يجب أن أرحل الآن.
Mommy, is it that you don't want me anymore?
أمي ، هل أنت لا تريدني بعد الآن؟
How could I not want you?
كيف لا اريدك
Even if the whole world doesn't want you,
حتى لو كان العالم كله لا يريدك ،
I definitely will want you.
بالتأكيد سأريدك.
Mommy, don't go.
أمي ، لا تذهب.
Be a good boy.
كن ولدا جيدا.
Listen to Miss An.
استمع إلى Miss An.
Wait for Mommy to come back to pick you up.
انتظر حتى تعود أمي لاصطحابك.
Mommy, don't go.
أمي ، لا تذهب.
♪The brush depicting you♪
الفرشاة التي تصور لك ♪
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪ كلاهما ضبابي وواضح ♪
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪ الرياح تهب فستانك ♪
♪You're like a poem♪
♪ أنت مثل القصيدة ♪
♪That captivates me♪
هذا يأسرني ♪
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪ أستمع إلى الريح وأنت بهدوء ♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
الممحاة التي أزالت براءتنا
♪I ask myself♪
♪ أسأل نفسي ♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪ أنت سبب مثابري ♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
اخترقت الظلام ♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪ لم نلتقي منذ بعض الوقت ♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
♪You broke through the darkness♪
اخترقت الظلام ♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪ لم نلتقي منذ بعض الوقت ♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
♪Waiting for you, in the future♪
في انتظارك في المستقبل ♪